offroaders.com 2013-05-17

# Contact Page - Offroaders.com

|  |     
  
---  
|  | 

**About Offroaders.com**

> **Offroaders.com, owned by Sliprock Media LLC, is dedicated to serve as a photo album to recount some of the off road adventures of a group of 4x4 enthusiasts.** **Along with our love for the off road adventure, we also try to present to our readers off road and 4x4 related information in the form of projects, product reviews, and links to other off road related sites such as 4x4 organizations and off road / outdoor product vendors.**   **Thanks for visiting and enjoy our little corner of the vast off road community.   All content within this site is presented for your amusement only.  Special thanks go to the friends and family of Maguire Products Inc. in Aston PA.  **

**Disclaimer: **

> **All content within this site is presented for your amusement only. All activities and vehicle modifications appearing or described within this website and on its pages may be potentially dangerous. We do not endorse or recommend any such activity or projects for others or to any particular person - we simply describe our experiences and our opinions. If you choose to engage in these activities or undertake any project, it is by your own free will and at your own volition. Always use common sense and remember that none of this material is presented as being recommended by a professional mechanic or driving instructor. This information is presented for your amusement only. Do not take unwise risks and always consult a certified professional if you are not sure of something.   Offroaders.com, Sliprock Media LLC, and the authors of these articles assume no liability for how any particular individual chooses to use the information presented here. **

**Offroaders.com Privacy Policy**

> **We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. When you submit your personally identifiable information on this Website, we will use the personally identifiable information you provide us only for the purpose of responding to any comments or questions you have.**

**Contact Offroaders**

> **If you wish to contact us here at Offroaders you may e-mail using the form below.   We appreciate your feedback and we try to answer your e-mail promptly.  All of the information you provide is confidential.**
> 
> **Before using the form below or emailing us, please review these few** **Frequently Asked Questions by clicking here:** ** Frequently Asked Questions**

**Club Listings**

> **CLUBS and ORGANIZATIONS ... Get Listed!   We offer FREE listings in our Clubs and Organizations Directory.   **
> 
> **Check out** **our new, improved Offroad Directory! Worldwide Offroad Clubs, 4x4 & automotive related links!  We are currently porting over the original pages of links to this new system, but browse what we have online so far and if you have a post you'd like to add, simply create an account and upload!**...  ** To the Links**

**Advertising on Offroaders.com**

> **Free Advertising!**
> 
> **If you have spent any time on Offroaders.com, you would notice that the site is primarily a content based website with articles, product information as well as a "just for fun" photo album.   As part of the information cornerstone of the site, we extent the offer of exchange to vendors and companies that is essentially free advertising for your company or product.   The exchange between Offroaders.com and you would be in the form of an article or information about your product or products, or simply general knowledge information.  The advertising for you would be credit to you for the article, your contact information, links back to your site and your products and exposure in a targeted market.  Articles and information are viewed daily by a large audience and the article remain online indefinitely without cost to you.   If you would like to discuss an exchange please contact us below.  Or for other forms of advertising, contact us below.**

| ** Your Information **   
All but name and email is optional ... however we can't reply without a **VALID** email address.   **Make sure the email address is correct.**   Too often we type up a reply, only to have it bounce back because the email address was typed incorrectly.  **So if you would like a reply, please double-check your email address.**

**Click here to review our Privacy Policy**  
_   _  
  
---  
    | **Name** |   
    | **E-Mail** |   
    | **City** |   
    | **State** |   
    | **Country** |   
    | **Your personal  
web page address:** |      
  
  | **Your Comments...**  

**     
CLUBS and ORGANIZATIONS ... **

> **Get Listed!   We offer FREE listings in our Clubs and Organizations Directory.  There's only one catch and that is that you exchange the favor and list us on your site.  Simple as that.  If you would like to see your club in our listings (Club Directory), please fill out the following information:**  
  
---  
  | **What Type of Club?** | 

|  | **ATV / Quad Club**  
---|---  
| **4x4 Vehicle / SUV Club**  
  
  | **Add or Update Listing?** | 

|  | **Add a Listing**  
---|---  
| **Update a Listing**  
  
    | **Club Name:** |   
    | **Web  Address:** |   
  | **Address (1):** |   
  | **Address (2):** |   
  | **Country  
(If Outside U.S.)** |   
  | **Email/Contact:** |   
  | **Phone :** |   
  | **Fax:** |   
    | **Clubs Base of Operation** | 

**Where am I?**

** Northeast ** \- The Northeast region includes: **Maine, Vermont, New Hampshire, Massachusetts, Rhode Island, Connecticut, New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Delaware, District of Columbia, Maryland, West Virginia, Virginia.**

**Southeast ** \- The Southeast region includes: **Florida, Georgia, Alabama, Mississippi, Tennessee, Arkansas, Louisiana, North Carolina, and South Carolina.**

**Midwest ** \- The Midwest region includes: **Minnesota, Wisconsin, Iowa, Illinois, Missouri, Michigan, Indiana, Ohio, and Kentucky**

**Northwest ** \- The Northwest region includes: **Nebraska, South Dakota, North Dakota, Montana, Wyoming, Idaho, Oregon, Washington**

**Southwest ** \- The Southwest region includes: **Nevada, Utah, Colorado, New Mexico, Kansas, Oklahoma, Arizona, Texas**

**California ** \- California has enough clubs to be a page all of its own.  

 **Canada ** \- North of the U.S. Border in any of the Canadian Provinces

**Mexico ** \- South of the U.S. Border

 ** International - ** All Other locations  
  
  | **Club or Organization description exactly as you would like to be listed.   Maximum number of characters is 300.**  
    |   |     
  |     
**Reciprocal Link to www.Offroaders.com  
If you're asking us to link to you, it's only fair you link back to us.  
Please give us the address where we might find the link.**  
  |   |   
  
#### Optional Survey information...  
This information is used to help us better design our site.   We appreciate your opinions and feedback.

#### What about offroaders.com do you enjoy?  
****

**What can we do to improve offroaders.com?  
**

#### 

#### **Search Engine: Other:               **

### Send in the form!

> * * *

> **Link to Offroaders.com \- If you would like to link to Offroaders.com here are a few Offroaders banners to choose from. Click Here**

* * *

**Frequently Asked Questions  
  **  
  
---  
**Q.** | **Can you tell me the location of the trails you have been to in the trail reports?**  
**A.** | **All of the locations in the trail reports are privately owned locations that we as a group had permission in some fashion to be on.   Most of the trail runs were organized through an off-road club or other 4x4 organization which was posted, if available, in the report itself.  With the exception of [Paragon Adventure Park](http://www.paragonap.com/), locations can not be disclosed due to the fact that they are private property.  Clubs who have organized events and make scheduled  trail runs are linked within the trail report.  Your best way to find out how you can find trails in your area is to join a local club and go on scheduled, organized events. ** **Check out our US Clubs section for a club near you.  If you are aware of trails in your area but need further details on those trails, your best bet is to study topography maps or satellite imagery.  For more info on these type of maps, see this link: Click Here. **  
**Q.** | **I have a site or I have a business that I would like Offroaders to link to.   Can you post my link?**  
**A.** | **You can send the link. If you are trading links (reciprocating a link) we will return the link to your site.  
    **  
  
**Back up to the Form**  
  
|  |
